uniqpaid.com 2019-08-16

# Privacy Policy - UniqPaid.com: Earn money for signing up for our FREE offers!

##### GENERAL:

UniqPaid strictly adheres to the Privacy Policy outlined below.  
We will closely guard any personally identifiable information you disclose to us during registration or at any other point during your uniqpaid.com experience. Information will only be shared with a third party if a member requests that such information be shared. 

By joining UniqPaid, you may choose between opting-in and opting-out from our Newsletters.  
You can unsubscribe from UniqPaid Mail at any time and still maintain an active UniqPaid account.  

##### WHAT INFORMATION DOES UNIQPAID COLLECT?:

In order to receive any payment from the UniqPaid service, we require all users to register via our online registration form. We require you to provide us with your full and correct name, full and correct street address, e-mail address and password. We will process this information to manage your membership, determine your eligibility, provide services, and allow you to take advantage of other member benefits. In addition to the information you provide to us in the online registration, we will also collect certain information online and offline arising out of your use of the UniqPaid service, including but not limited to the number and type of offers you have responded to and completed. 

UniqPaid.com will not share, sell, trade, or give away personally identifiable information to third parties without members' explicit permission.  
UniqPaid.com collects online behavior statistical information for our members. Upon termination of the online session, closing of the browser and/or termination of your membership, this information will no longer be collected. Summaries of the information will be made available to third parties. Those summaries do not include members' names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or other personally identifiable information. 

##### COOKIES:

UniqPaid uses a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to help save and retrieve passwords used on the UniqPaid.com and to save information on past activities and other preferences. 

With cookies you don't have to re-enter information upon every move throughout our site and you are able to complete offers without being prompted by our security system to log in again after each activity. When you log in to UniqPaid.com, UniqPaid reads the cookie to help target and personalize offers to you. UniqPaid uses cookies for the benefit of users. UniqPaid does not place any personally identifiable information in users' cookies. UniqPaid does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer. 

##### DATA SECURITY:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, UniqPaid uses appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. However, no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, UniqPaid cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us or from our sponsors and you do so at your own risk. 

##### LINK TO OTHER SITES:

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, UniqPaid.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the UniqPaid Web Site. 

##### OPTING-OUT:

Established members will occasionally receive e-mails containing information regarding new offers or special promotions from UniqPaid if they have not opted out. "Opting-out" means the user does not wish to receive such e-mails from UniqPaid.com. The opt-out can be performed upon initial registration or later. You may opt-out of receiving these newsletters at any time by updating your account information in the UniqPaid "Profile" section. You can reach the "Profile" section by clicking on the "Profile" link on the main page. When you reach this page, uncheck the box that reads, "Yes, I want to receive Special Cash Offers by e-mail." 

When a member receives an e-mail from UniqPaid.com and decides to no longer receive the e-mails, he or she can follow the following procedure. Open the e-mail and scroll to the bottom. At the bottom of the e-mail page there will be a brief description of how to have an account "opted-out." Once we receive information regarding these account changes we will make the specified changes as soon as possible. 

##### SITE AND SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENTS:

Under rare circumstances UniqPaid.com may need to contact specific or all users in order to make an important announcement about the UniqPaid site or service changes. Members are not able to un-subscribe, or "opt-out" of these announcements, because they may contain very important information regarding their accounts. Before these measures are taken, however, UniqPaid will post information regarding changes directly on the web site. UniqPaid.com reserves the right to contact users to correct account errors or to supply important information UniqPaid deems relevant. 

##### CORRECTION/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION:

UniqPaid users are able to change their personal information at any time. The fastest way to change personal information is to login to UniqPaid.com and simply click on "Profile". You will be prompted to enter your password again to change you personal information. If for some reason this page does not work, or there are any questions, users may contact our Member Support Team. Users should send our support team a clear and detailed e-mail message and our Member Support Team will see to it the proper changes are made to the user's account. 

##### SPAM:

We will immediately terminate any account which we believe, at our sole discretion, is transmitting or is otherwise connected with any Spam or other unsolicited bulk e-mails and postings. 

We will also pursue severe legal action against members who are involved in SPAM. These may include contacting respective authorities (employers, universities, local law-enforcement, the FBI) as well as asking Internet Service Providers to deny service. 

SPAM includes, but is not limited to, unsolicited e-mails and/or postings in discussion groups, bulletin boards, and other public domain groups. SPAM messages are generally prohibited by most network providers and certain jurisdictions and those users employing them may be subject to fines and/or imprisonment. We do not allow our members to utilize SPAM messages. The company will automatically terminate all spamming accounts. 

The only acceptable methods of referring someone to our UniqPaid.com Rewards Online Program are through communication with family and friends and by establishing a link to our web site on a member-owned web site. 

To report spam, send an e-mail to: [**abuse@uniqpaid.com**](emailto:abuse@uniqpaid.com)

##### CANCELING:

You may cancel your Membership at anytime by clicking on the "Terminate Account" button on the "Profile" section. If you do decide to cancel your membership, you can rejoin again at any time. 

##### CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY:

By registering to use the UniqPaid service, you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that UniqPaid' s privacy policy may change from time to time. We strongly advise our members to check back from time to time. We also welcome any feedback from you; please e-mail us at [**support@uniqpaid.com**](mailto:support@uniqpaid.com) if you have any comments regarding the information or improvements that can be made to this privacy policy.
